<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Juscep</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="developed_by_baseinfotech">Developed by BaseInfotech</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="sendotp_key">276051ArxlDBtgkXTd5cd54bcc</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="new_user_registration">New User Registration</string>
    <string name="login_details">Login Details</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="about_us_content">

    </string>
    <string name="about_us_top_text">
        India is developing country, along with all sectors infrastructure sector is gaining more importance now a days. As in the activities of construction or infrastructure development magnitude of the work and timely completion of work and quality control are very vital. In order to achieve this, we came into excistance to provide you all civil machinery and equipment solution on a single platform. With better technological equipment you will be able to cut down cost and lead time , which helps you to achieve the desired output in efficient and optomized manner.\n

To ease your works we are here to provide you better and more advanced heavey equipments in all over India . We are also offering business, If you are having the civil equipments and looking out to make business with it, Don\'t worry we are here to help you. \n
    </string>
    <string name="who_we_are_text">
        <b>JUSCEP</b> - The Machinery Rental Providers,Provides rental services of high-quality construction equipment.\n

As a part of india-based Machinery rental service (Registered by Govt.Of India),our goal is to go beyond the standard vendor relationship and create a true partnership with our customer by consistently Providing best-value solutions that get the job done.


    </string>
    <string name="rent_construction_text">
        1. Equipment is reliable and well maintained.\n
The units available for rent are inspected regularly and the hours of use are tracked.All equipment that has logged high numbers of hours is rotated out of circulation and replaced. All construction equipment available for rent at any time is in good condition and ready to go to work.\n\n

2. We provide the right machines at your construction area with local rates .\n
Many times it has been seen that local supplier demands a huge amount of money from outstation contractor.It\'s a compulsion for the contractor too to get the equipment on time.\n\n

3. Worry free operator service\n
Our supplier will provide the machine with well-trained operators. It becomes their responsibility of safety and maintenance of their machine.\n\n

4.	Rental equipment features the latest technology\n
To stay competitive,the rental company offers its newer models featuring the latest technology.By choosing to rent the equipment you need,you and your crew get the Opportunity to work with equipment with the latest features and benefits.As a result,you may be able to save time and money when completing your project.\n\n

5.	Rental means you can work with the right equipment\'s\n
You won\'t be stuck trying to make do with your existing equipment on a job site,renting gives you access to a complete inventory at your disposal.Choose exactly the piece of equipment you need.\n\n

6.	Renting equipment becoming more popular now a days\n
No one wants to buy the machines for a fraction of time.if they buy also,it\'s impossible to carry those machine to the construction site across the states.\n\n

7.	No capital investment needed.When you decide to rent construction equipment,the only time you will incur an expense is when you need it for a job\n
You\'re not typing up cash flow on a regular basis paying for financing costs.\n\n

8.	No need to worry about any kind of maintenance cost\n
These costs are the responsibility of the rental company. If something goes wrong while you Are using a piece of rental equipment,you can simply arrange to return it for a replacement. The rental company is responsible for any repairs,as well as general maintenance on all of its equipment.You do not have to account for maintenance expenses in your budget for that Place of machinery.\n\n

9.	You will get a chance to test the new model of the equipment before making any decision to buy it.\n
Reading about a piece of equipment\'s features and benefits doesn\'t always give you the true picture of what it would be like to operate it on a job site.if you are in the market for new Equipment, you can try out new models and get some "hands-on" experience before making Your final decision about which one is right for your business.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
